Humane Borders records, 2000-2010 MS 471
University of Arizona
- Series I: Media Files, 2000-2010
  - Subseries 1: News clippings, June 1, 2000-December 29, 2009
    - Tucson Citizen, Samaritans walk fine line in desert, June 4, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Tucson Citizen, Longtime agent takes over in Yuma, June 4, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Arizona Daily Star, Before setting out, crossers seek strength in church, June 4, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Tucson Citizen, U.S., Mexico target ‘corridor of death,’, June 4, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Arizona Daily Star, Mexico, U.S. plan to fortify border, June 4, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Arizona Daily Star, No right to cross border illegally, June 7, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Arizona Republic, Kolbe, Flake sound alarm on deaths, June 8, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - The Washington Times, June 11, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Twin-boro News, June 18, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Casa Grande Valley Newspaper, June 18, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - The Arizona Republic, June 19, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Tucson Citizen, Border Officers’ Bullets draw fire, June 19, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Arizona Daily Star, Clues from dead help provide identities, June 20, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - United Press International, June 20, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Frontera Hispana, Magnifica Labor social de parte del personal de Consulado de Mexico, June 20, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Frontera Hispana, ¿Quanto vale un vaso de agua?, June 20, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - Frontera Hispana, La Nacion Tohono O’odham y el agua samaritana, June 20, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - Frontera Hispana, Dirigentes de la tribu Tohono O’odham culpan a migrante de crisis, June 20, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Arizona Republic, Network seeks to staunch migrant deaths, June 25, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - The Miami Herald, Radiothon asks listeners to give ‘drop of hope’ for border crossings, June 26, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Arizona Daily Star, Death toll of entrants rises to 55, June 27, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Arizona Daily Star, U.S. draws Mexicans from nearly every town, June 27, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - Arizona Daily Star, O’odham Inauguration: Push for Progress, June 28, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - Tucson Citizen, ‘New Time’ for O’odham, June 28, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Houston Chronicle, Reservation proves harsh gateway for immigrants, June 29, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Tucson Citizen, Bringing down the wall, July 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Sojourners, July 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - Adelante, English and Spanish, July 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - Prensa Hispana, July 2, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 2, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - Arizona Republic, July 5, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - Tombstone Tumbleweed, July 10, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 11, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - Ventura County Star: National, July 12, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - Tucson Ctiizen, July 14, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 15, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - Homeland Ministries Newsletter, July 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - News Briefs, July 16, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - Christian Science Monitor, July 14, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 11, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - Sierra Vista Herald, July 11, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 17, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 17, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 17, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 17, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - Arizona Republic, July 17, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 17, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - PHX Media, July 18, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 163)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 19, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 21, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 22, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 166)
    - San Pedro Valley News-Sun, July 23, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 167)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 24, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 168)
    - KSDK News - Channel 5, July 24, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 169)
    - The New York Times, July 24, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 170)
    - Omaha World Herald, July 24, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 171)
    - The News Internatoinal, July 25, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 172)
    - U.S. News and World Report, July 28, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 173)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 30, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 174)
    - Arizona Republic, July 30, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 175)
    - Sierra Vista Herald, July 31, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 176)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 177)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 178)
    - The Connection, Arivaca, Arizona, August 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 179)
    - Sierra Vista Herald, August 2, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 180)
    - Sierra Vista Herald, August 3, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 181)
    - Chicago Tribune, August 3, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 182)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 4, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 183)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 4, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 184)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 4, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 185)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 4, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 186)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 9, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 187)
    - Yuma Sun, August 11, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 188)
    - Arizona Republic, August 11, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 189)
    - Yuma Sun, ¬August 11, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 190)
    - Kentucky.com, August 12, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 191)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 13, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 192)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 14, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 193)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 14, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 194)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 14, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 195)
    - Yuma Sun, August 15, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 196)
    - Arizona Daily Star, Caliente, August 15, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 197)
    - Washington Post, August 16, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 198)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 16, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 199)
    - Yuma Sun, August 20, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 200)
    - AILA Press Release, August 27, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 201)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 27, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 202)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 29, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 203)
    - TCU Alumni Newsletter, September 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 204)
    - NNIRR, September 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 205)
    - Hispanic Vista, September 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 206)
    - Maria Official Publication of Blessed Nuno Society, September 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 207)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 2, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 208)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 2, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 209)
    - Houston Chronicle, September 3, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 210)
    - Sierra Vista Herald, September 3, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 211)
    - Gannett News Service, September 4, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 212)
    - Arizona Republic, September 5, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 213)
    - Arizona Republic, September 8, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 214)
    - NTUF, September 9, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 215)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 9, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 216)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 9, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 217)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 9, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 218)
    - El Paso Times, September 10, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 219)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 14, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 220)
    - Yuma Sun, September 15, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 221)
    - Monterey Herald, September 16, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 222)
    - Arizona Republic, September 21, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 223)
    - Arizona Republic, September 21, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 224)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 22, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 225)
    - Arizona Republic, September 23, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 226)
    - The Sierra Times, September 25, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 227)
    - New York Times, September 25, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 228)
    - Arizona Hispanic, September 25, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 229)
    - Seoul Times, September 25, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 230)
    - Miami Herald, September 25, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 231)
    - Yuma Sun, September 25, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 232)
    - Terra, September 25, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 233)
    - National Border Patrol Council, September 25, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 234)
    - El Paso Times, September 26, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 235)
    - Front Page Magazine, September 26, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 236)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 26, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 237)
    - El Paso Times, September 26, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 238)
    - Arizona Republic, September 26, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 239)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 28, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 240)
    - LA Times, September 29, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 241)
    - Tucson Citizen, September 29, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 242)
    - Arizona Daily Star, September 29, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 243)
    - CCIS (The Center for Comparative Immigration Studies), October 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 244)
    - Catholic Vision Diocese of Tucson, October 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 245)
    - Sierra Vista Herald, October 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 246)
    - San Francisco SFgate.com, October 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 247)
    - Tucson Citizen, October 2, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 248)
    - Yuma Sun, October 4, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 249)
    - Tucson Citizen, October 4, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 250)
    - The Sun, October 7, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 251)
    - The Sun, October 8, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 252)
    - Radio Ondas "14,", October 9, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 253)
    - Arizona Republic, October 9, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 254)
    - Arizona Republic, October 11, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 255)
    - The Southern Border (also Arizona Republic), October 13, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 256)
    - Arizona Republic, October 16, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 257)
    - The Arizona Republic, October 16, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 258)
    - Arizona Republic, October 16, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 259)
    - Arizona Republic, October 16, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 260)
    - Denver Post, October 19, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 261)
    - Denver Post, October 19, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 262)
    - Useless-Knowledge.com, October 20, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 263)
    - LIRS, October 20, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 264)
    - Die Tageszeitung, October 25, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 265)
    - Arizona Republic, October 25, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 266)
    - Arizona Daily Star, October 26, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 267)
    - Spirit and Life, November 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 268)
    - KOCOA Knights of Columbus, November 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 269)
    - Hispanic Vista, November 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 270)
    - Arizona Daily Star, November 3, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 271)
    - United States District Court, November 4, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 272)
    - Arizona Republic, November 5, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 273)
    - USA Today, Also in Arizona Republic, November 5, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 274)
    - Tucson Citizen, November 5, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 275)
    - Arizona Republic, November 5, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 276)
    - Arizona Daily Star, November 5, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 277)
    - WLF.org, November 5, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 278)
    - Arizona Republic, November 6, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 279)
    - Naples Daily News, November 9, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 280)
    - The Arizona Republic, November 11, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 281)
    - The New York Times, November 11, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 282)
    - East Valley/Scottsdale Tribune, November 15, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 283)
    - Fundacion Mexico, November 15, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 284)
    - Tucson Citizen, November 17, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 285)
    - Arizona Republic Nogales Bureau, November 19, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 286)
    - National Catholic Reporter, November 21, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 287)
    - Yuma Sun, November 23, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 288)
    - The Arizona Republic, November 24, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 289)
    - Arizona Daily Star, November 25, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 290)
    - Sierra Vista Herald, November 25, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 291)
    - Sierra Vista Herald, November 25, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 292)
    - The Daily Dispatch Douglas, November 26, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 293)
    - Washington Dateline, November 27, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 294)
    - Arizona Republic Nogales Bureau, November 29, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 295)
    - Maryknoll, November 26, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 296)
    - Arizona Daily Star, November 30, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 297)
    - Intelligence Report, December 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 298)
    - Polemica, December 1, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 299)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 2, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 300)
    - Arizona Daily Star, December 2, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 301)
    - Tucson Citizen, December 3, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 302)
    - Tucson Citizen, December 4, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 303)
    - LA Weekly, Common Dreams News Center, December 5, 2003 - December 13, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 304)
    - The Palm Beach Post, December 7, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 305)
    - Tombstone Tumbleweed, December 11, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 306)
    - Vaterbottens Kuriren, December 12, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 307)
    - Star Telegram, December 12, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 308)
    - Sierra Vista Herald, December 13, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 309)
    - LiP Magazine, December 15, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 310)
    - Denver Catholic Register, December 17, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 311)
    - Tucson Citizen, December 17, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 312)
    - National Vanguard, December 20, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 313)
    - Newsletter of St. Mark’s Presbyterian Church, January 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - The Denver Post, January 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - BBC, January 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Giving, January 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Vivencias, January 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - PC (USA), January 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - La Fogata, January 3, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Sierra Vista Herald, January 3, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - NY Times, January 3, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - LiP Magazine, January 3, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - The Federal Oberver, January 6, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - MSNBC.com, January 7, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - White House, January 7, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - San Angelo Standard Times, also CNN News, January 7, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - CBSNews.com, January 7, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - NCLR, January 7, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - CNN.com, Fox News, U.S. News, San Diego Union Tribune, January 7, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 8, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 8, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Save the Planet, January 8, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - The Connection, Boston’s NPR, WBUR.org, January 8, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - KUED-7 Salt Lake City, January 10, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Arizona Daily Star, January 10, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Tucson Citizen, January 14, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Denver Post, January 16, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Diepresse, January 16, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Arizona Republic, January 30, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Knight Ridder Newspapers, January 31, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Star-Telegram Washington Bureau, February 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - U.S. Water News, February 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 3, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - St. Cloud Visitor, February 5, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - The Arizona Republic, February 16, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Tucson Citizen, February 18, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 21, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Tucson Citizen, February 21, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Tucson Citizen, February 21, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 24, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - La Voz, February 25, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Tucson Citizen, February 26, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Corvallis Gazette Times, February 27, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 28, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Arizona Daily Star, February 29, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Houston Catholic Worker, March 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Loaves and Fishes, March 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Spirit and Life, March 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - AFSC Voices from the Border, March 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 2, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Green Valley News and Sun, March 3, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Tombstone Tumbleweed, March 4, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Casa Grande Valley Newspaper, March 4, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 4, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Wabash College, March 5, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 5, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Tucson Citizen, March 8, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Tucson Citizen, March 8, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 9, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Protest Info, March 13, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Daily Sun - Flagstaff, March 14, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - New York Times, March 16, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - New York Times, March 16, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 16, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 17, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 17, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 17, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 17, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 20, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 20, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 22, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 25, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - ALAMY Images, March 27, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - New York Times, March 29, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Tucson Citizen Holding Pen, March 30, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 31, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Arizona Daily Star, March 31, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - MX Sin Fronteras, April 2004 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Disciples World, April 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Houston Chronicle, April 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 2004 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 3, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Tucson Citizen, April 7, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Arizona Republic, April 20, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Tucson Citizen, April 21, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Arizona Daily Star, April 24, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - AZCentral.com, April 24, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - Arizona Daily Wildcat, April 26, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Sierra Club, May 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - San Francisco Chronicle, May 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Ridgebury Congregational Church, May 2, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 3, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - MSNBC, May 3, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 4, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 4, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Christian Science Monitor, May 4, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - US Border Control, May 8, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 12, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - Tucson Weekly, May 13, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - The Washington Times, May 17, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - Sierra Vista, May 20, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 22, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - Arizona Republic, May 22, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 23, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - The Christian Science Monitor, May 25, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - MSNBC, May 25, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 104)
    - Tucson Citizen, May 28, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 105)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 28, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - Arizona Daily Star, May 30, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - MX Sin Frontera, June 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - Indymedia, June 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - Loaves and Fishes Borderlinks, June 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - The United Church of Christ - Southwest Conference, circa June 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 3, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 4, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 5, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 6, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - Albuquerque Tribune, June 7, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 117)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 7, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - KVOA Channel 4, June 8, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - Daily Pundit, June 8, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 8, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - Reuters, June 9, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 9, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - Presbyterian News Service, June 10, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 11, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 125)
    - Presbyterian News Service, June 11, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 126)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 12, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - America’s Debate, June 14, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 16, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - Tucson Weekly, June 17, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 22, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 22, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - VDARE, June 24, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - Tucson Citizen, June 25, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Arizona Republic, June 28, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - America, June 28, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - Arizona Daily Star, June 28, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - The Arizona Republic, June 28, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - Foster’s/Citizen Online, June 30, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 1, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 3, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 5, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Civil Homeland Defense, July 6, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - American Renaissance, July 8, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - La Prensa, July 10, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - Resource Center of the Americas, July 10, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - FINDLaw, July 12, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Diario La Estrella, July 12, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Fox News, July 13, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 13, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - WTOP Radio Network, July 13, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - Terra.com, July 14, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Tombstone Tumbleweed, July 15, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 19, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 19, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - Indymedia, July 23, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 24, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - CPT Arizona, July 25, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - Tucson Citizen, July 26, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Arizona Daily Star, July 27, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - Ikkevold Av Morten Ronning, July 27, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - Tucson Week, Thomas Whittingslow, July 29, 2004-August 4, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - Daily Herald, July 31, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 163)
    - Daily Herald, Laura Pohl, July 31, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 164)
    - The American Legion, Jeff Stoffen, August 2004 (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - Corvallis Gazette Times, Amanda Lee Myers, August 3, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 166)
    - The Star PM Update, Arizona Daily Star, August 4, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - The Brownsville Herald, August 8, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - First Coast News, August 9, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - MSNBC News, August 9, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 170)
    - The Christian Century, Rick Ufford-Chase, August 10, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - The Militant, August 17, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 172)
    - San Jose Mercury News, August 21, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 173)
    - USA Today, Arizona Republic, August 23, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 174)
    - Arizona Daily Star, August 24, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 175)
    - Tucson Citizen, August 24, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 176)
    - Asia Times, August 25, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 177)
    - Resource Center of the Americas, August 25, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 178)
    - Christian Science Monitor, EDC News, August 25, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 179)